kissed.co.za 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy » Mzansi Social Networking Community Best South African porn site

**Our Privacy Statement**

It is our firm policy to keep your personal information safe. We will not give out or share your information in any way, unless:   
You give us permission in advance   
We are ordered by a court of law   
We are committed to protecting the data used by our system, and utilize a rigid security system for this purpose. The only people with access to the information submitted on our site are our professional employees that manage your data for the sole purpose of giving you the information you request. 

**Cookies**

To better serve your needs, we collect cookies to confirm where our visitors are coming from. We do not observe the visitor’s website behavior, or store their personal information for personal or external uses. The information is only used to gain a better understanding of our advertising techniques and improve user experience. Cookies will expire 90 days after last visit. 

**Third party links**

Please be aware that the site may contain links to external websites. When you click these links, you will enter another site with different privacy policies and statements; for your protection we advise you to read these policies, which may differ from ours. 

**IP address**

To properly manage the site we use IP addresses to track user movement, watch developing trends, and assemble demographic data for composite use. 

**Web Beacons**

We use these transparent images to help personalize our website for your convenience. We may also use them to gain a better understanding of our customer’s behavior. 

**Online Survey Data**

From time to time we may offer voluntary surveys to help us enhance your experience. Your participation in these surveys gives us helpful information that will allow us to improve our website to your benefit. 

**Providing personal data to third parties**

Our services are offered through and accessible through a number of other websites in addition to this website. By signing up with the website and submitting data to or through the website you accept and acknowledge that all data that you submit to the website for access by members of the website may be searchable and available to users of the service who access it via different web sites from the website. We may also share information about you with third parties that we engage to help us in certain areas, such as payment providers, collection agencies, and email or newsletter senders. 

**Age Restrictions**

In our Terms and of Service we set our age restrictions. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, information from children under the age of 18, and any information sent to us from users we believe to be under this age will be permanently deleted from our database. 

**Privacy Statement Acceptance**

Please understand that the use of this website, to include disputes concerning privacy, is subject to our privacy statement and the Terms and Conditions of Service. By using our website, you are agreeing to the practices explained in the privacy statement and the applicable terms and conditions of service. We reserve the right to change or modify this privacy statement at any time, but if we do, the changes will be posted to this page and any other page deemed necessary. Your use of our website after the posting of the updated privacy statement will establish your acceptance of the change and/or modification. 

**Email**

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the unsubscribe or update profile links at the end of any email. 

**Feedback**

Listening to our members to ensure quality is what sets us apart from the rest. If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding privacy, please contact us! 

We understand that privacy and online security is of utmost importance, and we do everything we can to meet those needs. We take the feedback you provide us with very seriously, and will read every comment, complaint, and question you send.
